<iframe src="https://www.googletagmanager.com/ns.html?id=GTM-NK8XSV3&l=dataLayer" height="0" width="0" style="display:none;visibility:hidden"></iframe>

BREEZOMETER PRIVACY POLICY
==========================

Last Updated: October 1, 2023

In order to ensure transparency and give you more control over your Personal Information (as defined below), this privacy policy (“**Privacy Policy**”) governs how we, Breezometer Ltd. and its affiliates including Google LLC (together, “**Breezometer**” “**we**”, “**our**” or “**us**”) use, collect, and store Personal Data (as defined below) we collect or receive from or about you (“**you**”) such as in the following use cases:

1. When you browse or visit our website, [http://www.breezometer.com](https://www.breezometer.com/) (“**Website**”);
2. When you make use of, or interact with, our Website
    1. When you create an account and log in (API login) to the account dashboard
    2. When you request an evaluation
    3. When you subscribe to receive monthly updates about air quality and the internet of things
    4. When we process your job application
    5. When you contact us (e.g. customer support, need help, submit a request and/or answer our questions or surveys)
    6. When you use the Livemap feature available on our Website
3. When you make use of, or interact with, our mobile software application "Air Quality Index Breezometer", that we license (each individually, and collectively, the “**App**”).
    1. When you use the Livemap feature
    2. When you request to continuously update your personal exposure and/or to receive updates with the air quality is getting better or worse
    3. When you send us feedback
    4. When you utilize the "saved location" function (e.g., home, work)
4. When you attend a marketing event and provide us with your Personal Data and/or you exchange business cards with us
5. When we use the Personal Data of our customers (e.g. contact details)
6. When we use the Personal Data of our resellers, distributors, agents and/or finders (e.g. contact details)
7. When we use the Personal Data of our service providers (e.g. contact details)
8. When you interact with us on our social media profiles (e.g., Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, LinkedIn)

We greatly respect your privacy, which is why we make every effort to provide a platform that would live up to the highest of user privacy standards. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, so you can fully understand our practices in relation to Personal Data. “Personal Data” or “Personal Information” means any information that can be used, alone or together with other data, to uniquely identify any living human being. Please note that this is a master privacy policy and some of its provisions only apply to individuals in certain jurisdictions. For example, the legal basis in the table below is only relevant for GDPR-protected individuals.

**Important note**: Nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to limit in any way your statutory right, including your rights to a remedy or means of enforcement.

**Table of contents**:

1. What information we collect, why we collect it, and how it is used
2. How we protect and retain your Personal Data
3. How we share your Personal Data
4. Additional information regarding transfers of Personal Data
5. Your privacy rights
6. Use by children
7. Interaction with third party products
8. Log files
9. Analytic tools
10. Specific provisions applicable under California privacy law
11. Contact us

This Privacy Policy can be updated from time to time and, therefore, we ask you to check back periodically for the latest version of this Privacy Policy. If we implement significant changes to the use of your Personal Data in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you by posting a notice on our Website or by other means.

1. **WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT, WHY WE COLLECT IT, AND HOW IT IS USED**

|     |     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Specific Personal Data we collect** | **Why is the Personal Data collected and for what purposes?** | **Legal basis** | **Third parties with whom we share your Personal Data** | **Consequences of not providing the Personal Data** |
| **_When you browse or visit our Website_** |     |     |     |     |
| Cookies, analytic tools and log files.<br><br>For more information, please read our [cookies policy.](https://www.breezometer.com/cookies-policy) | For marketing, analytics and statistics purposes. | Consent<br><br>Legitimate interest (e.g., essential cookies) | 3rd party platforms such as for the following purposes:<br><br>* Google Analytics (analytic tool)<br>* Hubspot (CRM tool)<br>* LinkedIn (Ad Campaigns and referral traffic to site)<br>* Facebook (ad campaigns and referral traffic to site)<br>* Doubleclick (ad campaigns)<br>* Google (ad campaigns) | Certain Website features may not be available<br><br>Read more about the purposes of each cookie [here](https://www.breezometer.com/cookies-policy). |
| **_When you make use of, or interact with, our Website_** |     |     |     |     |
| **_When you create an account and when you log in (API login) to the account dashboard_** |     |     |     |     |
| * Full name<br>* Work email address<br>* Password<br>* Company URL<br>* When you subscribe to a premium version<br>* Any other information you may provide for us | * To be able to create an account<br>* To be able to log in to the account dashboard<br>* To be able to enjoy features available to registered or premium users only | Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party or in order to take steps at the request of the data subject prior to entering into a contract.<br><br>Legitimate interest (e.g. to log into the service). | 3rd party platforms such as for the following purposes:<br><br>* Hubspot Marketing Hub Professional - CRM and Marketing Automation<br>* Stripe and RevenueCat (payment methods) | Cannot create an account<br><br>Cannot log in<br><br>Cannot enjoy all the features |
| **_When you request an evaluation_** |     |     |     |     |
| * Full Name<br>* Work email address<br>* Company name<br>* Vertical<br>* Company URL | * To provide you with an evaluation of our product/services | Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party or in order to take steps at the request of the data subject prior to entering into a contract.<br><br>Legitimate interest (e.g., to provide an evaluation) | 3rd party platforms such as for the following purposes:<br><br>* Hubspot Marketing Hub Professional - CRM and Marketing Automation | Cannot provide you with an evaluation |
| **_When you subscribe to receive monthly updates about air quality and the internet of things_** |     |     |     |     |
| * Email addresses<br>* Full Name | * To send you monthly updates with information about how air pollution can affect you and updates regarding how environmental insights can improve the health of billions. | Consent<br><br>Legitimate interest (e.g. to allow you to post in our blog) | 3rd party platforms such as for the following purposes:<br><br>* Hubspot Marketing Hub Professional - CRM and Marketing Automation | Cannot email you our monthly update |
| **_When we process your job application_** |     |     |     |     |
| * Full Name<br>* Email address<br>* Phone number<br>* Department/position<br>* CV and cover letter<br>* Any other information you choose to share with us | * To process your job application<br>* To review your application<br>* To assess you as a candidate<br>* To analyze your application<br>* To communicate with you in connection with your job application | Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party or in order to take steps at the request of the data subject prior to entering into a contract<br><br>Legitimate interest (e.g. to process your job application) | 3rd party platforms such as for the following purposes:<br><br>* Hubspot Marketing Hub Professional- CRM and Marketing Automation<br>* Gsuit for scheduling interviews and contacting user | Cannot process your job application<br><br>Cannot review your application<br><br>Cannot assess you as a candidate<br><br>Cannot analyze your application<br><br>Cannot communicate with you in connection with your job application |
| **_When you contact us (e.g. customer support, need help, submit a request and/or answer our questions or surveys)_** |     |     |     |     |
| * Full Name<br>* Email address<br>* Company URL and work email address<br>* Industry<br>* Country<br>* Answers to our questions and/or surveys (available on our website from time to time)<br>* In case that you voluntarily participate on a survey and/or answer questions published by us, we collect the user ID (provided by the third party provider (e.g., Hotjar))<br>* Any other information you choose to share with us | * To process your request<br>* To provide you with assistance<br>* To respond to your query<br>* To allow you to answer the surveys and/or questions that we publish (the answers are voluntarily) | Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party or in order to take steps at the request of the data subject prior to entering into a contract<br><br>Legitimate interest (e.g. to respond to a query sent by you) | 3rd party platforms such as for the following purposes:<br><br>* Hubspot Marketing Hub Professional - CRM and Marketing Automation<br>* Hotjar - performance tool and analytics | Cannot process your request<br><br>Cannot provide assistance<br><br>Cannot respond to your query |
| **_When you use the LiveMap feature available on our Website_** |     |     |     |     |
| * Geo-location data<br>* IP address | * To provide you with information about air quality and exposure in the place that you are located<br>* Provide alerts about fires around you. | Consent<br><br>Legitimate interest (e.g. to allow you to access location specific information) | 3rd party platforms such as for the following purposes:<br><br>* Mapbox- map loads for web<br>* Here technologies – a tool to convert the long lat to address and search capabilities<br>* Openstreetmap-Nominatim- a tool for geocoding and reverse geocoding<br>* Sisense - Sisense Business Intelligence and Analytics software | Cannot provide you with air quality and exposure information<br><br>Cannot send you location specific air quality alerts<br><br>Cannot send you alerts about fires around you<br><br>Cannot collect air quality data in order to update your personal exposure |
| **_When you make use of, or interact with, the App_** |     |     |     |     |
| **_When you download the App, log in and make use of the App_** |     |     |     |     |
| * IP address<br>* Picture<br>* When you subscribe to a premium version<br><br>Any other information you may provide for us with (all the below information is optional)<br><br>* Description of any allergies you or your family members have (e.g., if you have Asthma, or if you are pregnant)<br>* Description of any family members with respiratory diseases (e.g., if any of your children suffer from respiratory diseases)<br>* Description of the environment around you, which does not include Personal Data | * To be able to download the App<br>* To be able to enjoy features available to registered or premium users only<br>* To customize your experience<br>* To provide you with relevant alerts<br>* To allow you to evaluate the impact of your environment surrounding you and your family<br><br>Please note that the descriptions of the environment around you may be displayed in the App for all users, however, such information does not include Personal Data. This information is stored locally in your device. | Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party<br><br>Legitimate interest (e.g. to log into the App or to allow you to receive alerts relevant to your interests). | 3rd party platforms such as for the following purposes:<br><br>* FireBase analytics<br>* Stripe and RevenueCat (payment methods)<br>* Flurry – Analytic tool | Cannot download the App<br><br>Cannot enjoy features available to registered users only<br><br>Cannot customize your experience<br><br>Cannot provide you with relevant alerts<br><br>Cannot allow you to evaluate the impact of your environment surrounding you and your family |
| * Geolocation (longitude and latitude coordinates only) | * To provide you information about the air quality and exposure of the user's current location<br>* To collect air quality data in order to update the personal exposure of the user<br>* To provide your with the pollen feature (when requested by you)<br>* To provide you with the Weather feature (when requested by you) | Consent | 3rd party platforms such as for the following purposes:<br><br>* Mapbox- map loads for web<br>* Here technologies – a tool to convert the long lat to address and search capabilities<br>* Openstreetmap-Nominatim- a tool for geocoding and reverse geocoding<br>* Google Analytics- analytics tool<br>* Google Firebase - to store the data | Cannot provide you information about the air quality and exposure of the user's current location<br><br>Cannot collect air quality data in order to update the personal exposure of the user<br><br>Cannot provide you with the Pollen feature (when requested by you)<br><br>Cannot provide you with the Weather feature (when requested by you) |
| Breezometer does not collect any Personal Data in the context of this feature | * We allow you to share the quality air and Breezometer’s App link with your friends | Legitimate interest (e.g. when you proactively decide to share the link of Breezometer’s App with your friends) | 3rd party platforms such as for the following purposes:<br><br>* smatURL (tool to allow you to share the URL in social media channels) | Cannot share the quality air and Breezometer’s App link with your friends |
| **_When you use the Livemap feature_** |     |     |     |     |
| * User Identifier (anonymous manner)<br>* IP address or MAC address<br>* Device name and details, to the extent that includes Personal Data | * To provide you with information about air quality and exposure in the place that the user is located.<br>* To show you about the closest fires to your location. | Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party or in order to take steps at the request of the data subject prior to entering into a contract<br><br>Legitimate interest (e.g. to allow you to access location specific information) | 3rd party platforms such as for the following purposes:<br><br>* Google Analytics for app analytics<br>* Sisense - Sisense Business Intelligence and Analytics software<br>* Google Firebase - to store the data | Cannot provide you with air quality and exposure information<br><br>Cannot show you about the closest fires to your location. |
| **_When you request to continuously update your personal exposure and/or to receive updates with the air quality is getting better or worse_** |     |     |     |     |
| * Geolocation (longitude and latitude coordinates only)<br>* Device name and details (for example Samsung S10, OS version 8), to the extent that includes Personal Data | * When you proactively activate this feature, the App collects location data even when the app is closed or not in use, in order to enable us to continuously update your personal exposure and/or to receive updates when the air quality is getting better or worse (background data access). | Consent (the user can activate this feature by the permissions available in the App. Users can withdraw permission at any time) | 3rd party platforms such as for the following purposes:<br><br>* Mapbox- map loads for web<br>* Here technologies – a tool to convert the long lat to address and search capabilities<br>* Google Analytics for app analytics Google Firebase - to store the data | Cannot provide you with information about your exposure<br><br>Cannot provide you with updates regarding air quality |
| **_When you send us feedback and/or contact us by email_** |     |     |     |     |
| * Email address<br>* Feedback and/or comments<br>* Any other information you choose to share with us, to the extent that it contains Personal Data | * To provide us with feedback regarding the App<br>* To allow you to ask us questions<br>* To improve the App<br>* To provide you with a better service | Legitimate interest (e.g. when you decide to send us feedback and comments) | 3rd party platforms such as for the following purposes:<br><br>* Google Analytics for app analytics<br>* Gsuit – email provider | * Cannot provide us with your feedback.<br>* Cannot ask us questions<br>* Cannot improve the App<br>* Cannot provide you with a better service |
| **_When you utilize the "saved location" function (e.g.. home, work)_** |     |     |     |     |
| * Geolocation (long and lat)<br>* Comments that you add to the air quality, to the extent that includes Personal Data<br>* Device name and details, to the extent that includes Personal Data | * To enable you to save your favorite locations (we only save the long-lat but you cannot write details for such location)<br>* To show you the address saved by you as favorite in the App. For avoidance of doubt, we do not store the specific address, we only store long-lat<br>* To provide you with the Weather feature (when requested by you)<br>* To provide your with the pollen feature (when requested by you)<br><br>Note: For the avoidance of doubt, we do not store the specific address, we only store longitude and latitude coordinates | Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party or in order to take steps at the request of the data subject prior to entering into a contract<br><br>Legitimate interest (e.g. to allow you to save locations) | 3rd party platforms such as for the following purposes:<br><br>* Google Analytics for app analytics<br>* Google Firebase - to store the data<br>* Mapbox- map loads for web<br>* Here technologies – a tool to convert the long lat to address and search capabilities | Cannot save your favorite locations (we only save the long-lat but you cannot write details for such location)<br><br>Cannot show you the address saved by you as favorite in the App. For avoidance of doubt, we do not store the specific address, we only store long-lat<br><br>Cannot provide you with the Weather feature (when requested by you)<br><br>Cannot provide your with the pollen feature (when requested by you) |
| **_When you attend a marketing event and provide us with your Personal Data and/or you exchange business cards with us_** |     |     |     |     |
| * Full name<br>* Email address<br>* Phone number<br>* Any other information you choose to share with us | * To establish a business connection<br>* To send you marketing communications | Depending on the context, consent or legitimate interest (e.g., to send you more information about Breezometer) or pre-contractual discussions | 3rd party platforms such as for the following purposes:<br><br>* Hubspot Marketing Hub Professional - CRM and Marketing Automation<br>* Sisense Business Intelligence and Analytics software | Cannot send you marketing communications<br><br>Cannot establish a business connection |
| **_When we use the Personal Data of our customers (e.g. contact details)_** |     |     |     |     |
| * Full name<br>* Email address<br>* Phone number<br>* Company Name<br>* Position at company<br>* Any other information you choose to share with use | * To communicate with customers<br>* To perform the applicable agreement | Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which our customer is a party.<br><br>Compliance with a legal obligation (e.g. tax laws, bookkeeping laws, etc.).<br><br>Legitimate interest (e.g. send you contract-related communications) | 3rd party platforms such as for the following purposes:<br><br>* Hubspot Marketing Hub Professional - CRM and Marketing Automation<br>* Sisense Business Intelligence and Analytics software | Cannot communicate with Customers<br><br>Cannot perform applicable agreement |
| * Full name<br>* Email address | * To send marketing updates | Consent | * Hubspot Marketing Hub Professional - CRM and Marketing Automation | Cannot send marketing updates |
| **_When we use the Personal Data of our resellers, distributors, agents and/or finders (e.g. contact details)_** |     |     |     |     |
| * Full name<br>* Email address<br>* Phone number<br>* Position at company<br>* Any other info that you choose to share with us | * To communicate with our resellers, distributors, agents and/or finders<br>* To perform the applicable agreement<br>* To send you contract-related communications | Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party or in order to take steps at the request of the data subject prior to entering into a contract<br><br>Legitimate interest (e.g. perform the contract, send contract-related communications) | 3rd party platforms such as for the following purposes:<br><br>* Hubspot Marketing Hub Professional - CRM and Marketing Automation<br>* Sisense Business Intelligence and Analytics software | Cannot communicate with our resellers, distributors, agents, and/or finders<br><br>Cannot perform the applicable agreement<br><br>Cannot send you contract-related communications |
| **_When we use the Personal Data of our service providers (e.g. contact details)_** |     |     |     |     |
| * Full name<br>* Email address<br>* Phone number<br>* Position at company<br>* Company Name<br>* Any other info that you choose to share with us | * To communicate with our service providers<br>* To perform the applicable agreement<br>* To send you contract-related communications | Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party or in order to take steps at the request of the data subject prior to entering into a contract<br><br>Legitimate interest (e.g. perform the contract, send contract-related communications) | 3rd party platforms such as for the following purposes:<br><br>* Hubspot Marketing Hub Professional - CRM and Marketing Automation<br>* Sisense Business Intelligence and Analytics software | Cannot communicate with our service providers<br><br>Cannot perform the applicable agreement<br><br>Cannot send you contract-related communications |
| **_When you interact with us on our social media profiles (e.g., Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn)_** |     |     |     |     |
| * Name/user name<br>* Email address<br>* Any information that you wish to share with us | * To allow you to communicate with us<br>* To answer your queries | Depending on the context, legitimate interest (e.g. replying your requests/questions), pre-contractual discussions (e.g. if you request us to send you more information of our products/services) or consent | 3rd party platforms such as for the following purposes:<br><br>* Hubspot Marketing Hub Professional - CRM and Marketing Automation<br>* Sisense Business Intelligence and Analytics software Facebook for the purpose of communicating with you<br>* LinkedIn for the purpose of communicating with you<br>* Twitter for the purpose of communicating with you | Cannot communicate with you<br><br>Cannot provide you with necessary marketing/product/services information |

Finally, please note that some of the abovementioned Personal Data will be used for detecting, taking steps to prevent, and prosecution of fraud or other illegal activity, to identify and repair errors, to conduct audits, and for security purposes. Personal Data may also be used to comply with applicable laws, with investigations performed by the relevant authorities, law enforcement purposes, and/or to exercise or defend legal claims. In certain cases, we may or will anonymize or de-identify your Personal Data and further use it for internal and external purposes, including, without limitation, to improve the services and for research purposes. “Anonymous Information” means information which does not enable identification of an individual user, such as aggregated information about the use of our services. We may use Anonymous Information and/or disclose it to third parties without restrictions (for example, in order to improve our services and enhance your experience with them).

4. HOW WE PROTECT AND RETAIN YOUR INFORMATION
    1. Security. We have implemented appropriate technical, organizational and security measures designed to protect your personal data. However, please note that we cannot guarantee that the information will not be compromised as a result of unauthorized penetration to our servers. As the security of information depends in part on the security of the computer, device or network you use to communicate with us and the security you use to protect your user IDs and passwords, please make sure to take appropriate measures to protect this information.
    2. Retention of your Personal Data. In addition to the retention periods mentioned above, in some circumstances we may store your Personal Data for longer periods of time, for example (i) where we are required to do so in accordance with legal, regulatory, tax or accounting requirements, or (ii) for us to have an accurate record of your dealings with us in the event of any complaints or challenges, or (iii) if we reasonably believe there is a prospect of litigation relating to your Personal Data or dealings. We have an internal data retention policy to ensure that we do not retain your Personal Data perpetually. Regarding retention of cookies, you can read more in our [cookie policy](https://www.breezometer.com/cookies-policy).
5. HOW WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL DATA
    
    In addition to the recipients described above, we may share your Personal Data as follows:
    
    1. With our business partners with whom we jointly offer products or services. We may also share Personal Data with our affiliated companies.
    2. To the extent necessary, with regulators, courts or competent authorities, to comply with applicable laws, regulations and rules (including, without limitation, federal, state or local laws), and requests of law enforcement, regulatory and other governmental agencies or if required to do so by court order;
    3. If, in the future, we sell or transfer, or we consider selling or transferring, some or all of our business, shares or assets to a third party, we will disclose your Personal Data to such third party (whether actual or potential) in connection with the foregoing events;
    4. In the event that we are acquired by, or merged with, a third party entity, or in the event of bankruptcy or a comparable event, we reserve the right to transfer, disclose or assign your Personal Data in connection with the foregoing events; and/or
    5. Where you have provided your consent to us sharing or transferring your Personal Data (e.g., where you provide us with marketing consents or opt-in to optional additional services or functionality).
6. ADDITIONAL INFORMATION REGARDING TRANSFERS OF PERSONAL DATA
    1. Storage: We store our data in Hubspot CRM. The HubSpot platform is hosted in data center providers in the US - Amazon Web Services in the US-East-1 region. Google Cloud Platform- data stored here is located in the US.
    2. Internal transfers: Transfers within the Breezometer Group will be covered by an internal processing agreement entered into by members of the Breezometer Group (an intra-group agreement) which contractually obliges each member to ensure that Personal Data receives an adequate and consistent level of protection wherever it is transferred to.
    3. External transfers: Where we transfer your Personal Data outside of the European Union (including the European Economic Area) (“EU”), the United Kingdom and Switzerland (for example to third parties who provide us with services), we will obtain contractual commitments from them to protect your Personal Data. When we engage in such transfers of personal information, we may rely on i) Adequacy Decisions as adopted by European Commission on the basis of Article 45 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (GDPR) (for example, when we access from Israel), ii) the Data Privacy Framework described below, or iii) Standard Contractual Clauses issued by the European Commission. We also continually monitor the circumstances surrounding such transfers in order to ensure that these maintain, in practice, a level of protection that is essentially equivalent to the one guaranteed by applicable law, such as the GDPR.  
        Data Privacy Framework: As described in our parent company Google LLC’s [Data Privacy Framework certification](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/participant-search/participant-detail?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI), we comply with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (“EU-U.S. DPF”), the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (collectively, the “Data Privacy Framework” or “DPF”), as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information received in the U.S. from the EU, the United Kingdom, and Switzerland in reliance on the DPF. Google LLC and its wholly owned US subsidiaries has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the DPF Principles. Breezometer remains responsible for any of your personal information that is shared under the Accountability for Onward Transfer Principle with third parties for external processing on our behalf, as described in the “How We Share Your Personal Data” section. To learn more about the DPF certification program, and to view our parent company Google LLC’s certification, please visit the [Data Privacy Framework website](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/). If you have an inquiry or complaint regarding our privacy practices in relation to our DPF certification, we encourage you to contact us at [privacy@breezometer.com](mailto:privacy@breezometer.com). Google is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (“FTC”). You may also refer a complaint to your local data protection authority, and we will work with them to resolve your concern. In certain circumstances, the Data Privacy Framework provides the right to invoke binding arbitration to resolve complaints not resolved by other means, as described in Annex I to the [Data Privacy Framework Principles](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/article/ANNEX-I-introduction-dpf?tabset-35584=2.).
7. YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS. HOW TO DELETE YOUR ACCOUNT
    1. Rights: The following rights (which may be subject to certain exemptions or derogations) shall apply to certain individuals (some of which only apply to individuals protected by the GDPR):
        
        * You have a right to access Personal Data held about you. Your right of access may normally be exercised free of charge, however we reserve the right to charge an appropriate administrative fee where permitted by applicable law;
        * You have the right to request that we rectify any Personal Data we hold that is inaccurate or misleading;
        * You have the right to request the erasure/deletion of your Personal Data (e.g. from our records). Please note that there may be circumstances in which we are required to retain your Personal Data, for example for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims;
        * You have the right to object, to or to request restriction, of the processing;
        * You have the right to data portability. This means that you may have the right to receive your Personal Data in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, and that you have the right to transmit that data to another controller;
        * You have the right to object to profiling;
        * You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Please note that there may be circumstances in which we are entitled to continue processing your data, in particular if the processing is required to meet our legal and regulatory obligations. Also, please note that the withdrawal of consent shall not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal;
        * You also have a right to request certain details of the basis on which your Personal Data is transferred outside the European Economic Area, but data transfer agreements and/or other details may need to be partially redacted for reasons of commercial confidentiality;
        * You have a right to lodge a complaint with your local data protection supervisory authority (i.e., your place of habitual residence, place or work or place of alleged infringement) at any time or before the relevant institutions in your place of residence. We ask that you please attempt to resolve any issues with us before you contact your local supervisory authority and/or relevant institution.
        
        You can exercise your rights by contacting us at [privacy@breezometer.com](mailto:privacy@breezometer.com). Subject to legal and other permissible considerations, we will make every reasonable effort to honor your request promptly in accordance with applicable law or inform you if we require further information in order to fulfil your request. When processing your request, we may ask you for additional information to confirm or verify your identity and for security purposes, before processing and/or honoring your request. We reserve the right to charge a fee where permitted by law, for instance if your request is manifestly unfounded or excessive. In the event that your request would adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others (for example, would impact the duty of confidentiality we owe to others) or if we are legally entitled to deal with your request in a different way than initial requested, we will address your request to the maximum extent possible, all in accordance with applicable law.
        
    2. Deleting your account: Should you ever decide to delete your account, you may do so by emailing privacy@breezometer.com. If you terminate your account, any association between your account and Personal Data we store will no longer be accessible through your account. However, given the nature of sharing on certain services, any public activity on your account prior to deletion will remain stored on our servers and will remain accessible to the public.
8. USE BY CHILDREN
    
    We do not offer our products or services for use by children and, therefore, we do not knowingly collect Personal Data from, and/or about children under the age of eighteen (18). If you are under the age of eighteen (18), do not provide any Personal Data to us without involvement of a parent or a guardian. For the purposes of the GDPR, we do not intend to offer information society services directly to children. In the event that we become aware that you provide Personal Data in violation of applicable privacy laws, we reserve the right to delete it. If you believe that we might have any such information, please contact us at [privacy@breezometer.com](mailto:privacy@breezometer.com).
    
9. INTERACTION WITH THIRD PARTY PRODUCTS
    
    We enable you to interact with third party websites, mobile software applications and products or services that are not owned or controlled by us (each a “Third Party Service”). We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Third Party Services. Please be aware that Third Party Services can collect Personal Data from you. Accordingly, we encourage you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policies of each Third Party Service.
    
10. LOG FILES
    
    We use log files. We use such information to analyze trends, administer the Website, track users’ movement around the Website, and gather demographic information.
    
11. ANALYTIC TOOLS
    
    * Google Analytics. The Website uses a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of the Website. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this Website, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other websites they used prior to coming to this Website. We use the information we get from Google Analytics to maintain and improve the Website and our products. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with Personal Information we collect. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this Website is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Service, available at [https://marketingplatform.google.com/about/analytics/terms/us/](https://marketingplatform.google.com/about/analytics/terms/us/), and the Google Privacy Policy, available at [http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). You may learn more about how Google collects and processes data specifically in connection with Google Analytics at [http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). You may prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics by downloading and installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on, available at [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).
        
    * Firebase Analytics. We also use “Google Analytics for Firebase”. By enabling this tool, we enable the collection of data about App Users, including via [identifiers for mobile devices](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) (including Android Advertising ID and Advertising Identifier for iOS), cookies and similar technologies. We use the information we get from Google Analytics for Firebase to maintain and improve our App(s). We do not facilitate the merging of personally-identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information unless we have robust notice of, and your prior affirmative (i.e., opt-in) consent to, that merger. Finally, please note that Google Analytics for Firebase’s terms (available at [https://firebase.google.com/terms/](https://firebase.google.com/terms/)) shall also apply.
        
    * Facebook Pixels and SDKs. We use Facebook pixels or SDKs, which are tools that provide help to website owners and publishers, developers, advertisers, business partners (and their customers) and others integrate, use and exchange information with Facebook, as such the collection and use of information for ad targeting. Please note that third parties, including Facebook, use cookies, web beacons, and other storage technologies to collect or receive information from your websites and elsewhere on the internet and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads. Facebook’s ability to use and share information is governed by the Facebook Tools Terms, available at: [https://www.facebook.com/legal/technology\_terms/.](https://www.facebook.com/legal/technology_terms/) You can prevent your data from being used by Facebook Pixels and SDKs by exercising your choice through these mechanisms: [http://www.aboutads.info/ c](http://www.aboutads.info/)hoices o[r http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/.](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)
        
    * Facebook Custom Audience
    * "Flurry", powered by Yahoo: Flurry’s ability to use and share information is governed by Flurry’s privacy policy, available at https://legal.yahoo.com/us/en/yahoo/privacy/products/developer/index.html. You may choose to opt out of the Flurry services via the Flurry Opt-Out Page, available at [https://dev.flurry.com/secure/optOut.do](https://dev.flurry.com/secure/optOut.do). We have incorporated an additional link which further elaborates on managing Opt Outs https://thenai.org/opt-out/.
    * Advertising Partners. Through our services, we allow third party advertising partners to set technologies and other tracking tools to collect information regarding your activities and your device (e.g., your IP address, mobile/website identifiers, page(s) visited, location, time of day). We also combine and share such information and other information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) with third party advertising partners. These advertising partners will use this information (and similar information collected from other websites) for purposes of delivering targeted advertisements to you when you visit third party websites within their networks. This practice is commonly referred to as “interest-based advertising” or “online behavioral advertising. We allow access to other data collected by the services to share information that may be useful, relevant, valuable or otherwise of interest to you. If you prefer not to share your Personal Information with third party advertising partners, you may let us know.

    We reserve the right to remove or add new analytic tools.
    
12. SPECIFIC PROVISIONS APPLICABLE UNDER CALIFORNIA PRIVACY LAW
    1. Our California Do Not Track Notice: Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that users can set in certain web browsers. Please note that we do not respond to or honor DNT signals or similar mechanisms transmitted by web browsers.
    2. Deletion of Content from California Residents: If you are a California resident under the age of 18 and a registered user, California Business and Professions Code Section 22581 permits you to remove content or personal information you have publicly posted. If you wish to remove such content or personal information and you specify which content or personal information you wish to be removed, we will do so in accordance with applicable law. Please be aware that after removal you may not be able to restore removed content. In addition, such removal does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or personal information you have posted and that there may be circumstances in which the law does not require us to enable removal of content.
13. CONTACT US
    
    If you have any questions, concerns or complaints regarding our compliance with this notice and the data protection laws, or if you wish to exercise your rights, we encourage you to first contact us at [privacy@breezometer.com](mailto:privacy@breezometer.com).

#### About BreezoMeter

#### Company
